Guide to the Alan Pryce-Jones Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Correspondence, 1876-1996; Series I; 11.5; (28 boxes)
  - ALAN PRYCE-JONES CORRESPONDENCE
    - Hill, Derek, 1958-88, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 585)
      Accompanied by photograph of APJ
      with unidentified woman, 1988
    - Hilles, Frederick C., 1953 Jun 26 (Box 12, Folder 586)
    - Hillier, Bevis, 1976-87 (Box 12, Folder 587)
    - Hinde, Thomas, 1963 Jan 17 (Box 12, Folder 588)
    - Hines, Betty, 1961, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 589)
    - Hinks, R. P., 1940-50 (Box 12, Folder 590)
    - Hinsley, F. H., n.d. (Box 12, Folder 591)
    - History Today
      See: Peter Quennell, Box 21, folder 1006
    - Hodgkin, Eliot, 1931 Nov 20 (Box 12, Folder 592)
    - Hoffman, Gale, 1961-62 (Box 12, Folder 593)
    - Hogan, Charles Beecher, 1961 Jul 29 (Box 12, Folder 594)
    - [Hohenlohe?], Elisabeth, 1956-57, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 595)
    - Hollis and Carter Ltd., 1961 Feb 2 (Box 12, Folder 596)
    - Hollis, Christopher, 1947-65, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 597)
    - Holloway, John, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 598)
    - Holman-Hunt, Diana (Diana Cuthbert), n.d. (Box 12, Folder 599)
    - Holroyd, Michael, 1965-66 (Box 12, Folder 600)
    - Holt, Rinehart and Winston, Inc., 1960-62 (Box 12, Folder 601)
    - Hone, Joseph, 1949, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 602)
    - Honeyborne, Rose, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 603)
    - Honour, Hugh, 1967 Mar 22 (Box 12, Folder 604)
    - Hope, Anthony (Anthony Hope Hawkins), 1932 May 16 (Box 12, Folder 605)
    - Hope, Francis, 1958-66, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 606)
    - Hopkins, Gerard, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 607)
    - Horizon, 1961 (Box 12, Folder 608)
      See also: Cyril Connolly, Box 7, folder 293
    - Horler, Sydney, 1948 Jul 17 (Box 12, Folder 609)
    - Horner, David, 1933-69, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 610)
      Some letters contain postscripts
      from Osbert Sitwell
    - Horovitz, Michael, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 611)
    - Hough, Graham Goulden, 1952 Aug 4 (Box 12, Folder 612)
    - Houghton, Mifflin and Company, 1946-66 (Box 12, Folder 613)
    - House and Garden, 1962 Sep 24 (Box 12, Folder 614)
    - Howard, Brian, 19[31]-40, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 615)
    - Howarth, Patrick, 1962 Oct 15 (Box 12, Folder 616)
    - [Howden?], Richard; "Clare", 1960, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 617)
    - Hughes, Langston, 1965 May 4 (Box 12, Folder 618)
    - Hulshizer, Lyle Roy, 1987, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 619)
    - Hussey, Christopher, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 620)
    - The Hutchinson Publishing Group, 1961 Oct 25 (Box 12, Folder 621)
    - Hutton, Graham, 1947 Oct 5 (Box 12, Folder 622)
    - Huxley, Julian, 1954 Apr 14 (Box 12, Folder 623)
    - Hyun, Peter, 1960 Mar 24 (Box 12, Folder 624)
    - "I" general, 1955-94, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 625)
    - Ilchester, Giles Stephen Holland Fox-Strangways, Earl of, 1955-56, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 626)
    - The Independent, 1990-94 (Box 12, Folder 627)
    - Ionesco, Eugène, 1955 Jan 18 (Box 12, Folder 628)
    - Irvine, Gerard, 1989, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 629)
    - "J" general, 1931-87, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 630)
    - Jack, Ian, 1985 Apr 20 (Box 12, Folder 631)
    - Jacob, E. F., 1955 Dec 13 (Box 12, Folder 632)
    - James, Bruno S., n.d. (Box 12, Folder 633)
    - Jameson, Storm (Margaret Storm), 1952 Aug 20 (Box 12, Folder 634)
    - Jarka, Horst, 1962 Oct 15 (Box 12, Folder 635)
    - Jeffs, Julian, 1969 Nov 17 (Box 12, Folder 636)
    - Jellicoe, Patricia, Countess of, 1975-95 (Box 12, Folder 637)
    - Jenkins, Elizabeth, 1954 Jul 17 (Box 12, Folder 638)
    - Jennings, Richard, 1932-50 (Box 12, Folder 639)
    - Joad, C. E. M., 1949-52, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 640)
    - Johansen, Gert, 1967-86, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 641)
      Letter of 1979 May 24 encloses
      photographs of his furniture
      shop in Copenhagen
    - John Murray (Publishers), 1942-72 (Box 12, Folder 642)
    - Johnson, Philip, 1961-62 (Box 12, Folder 643)
    - Joint Broadcasting Committee, 1940 (Box 12, Folder 644)
    - Joll, James, 1964 Mar 30 (Box 12, Folder 645)
    - Jones, Alexander, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 646)
    - Jones, Alfred Winslow; Jones, Mary, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 647)
    - Jones, David, 1955-58 (Box 12, Folder 648)
    - Jones, Evelyn, Lady, 1943-65, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 649)
    - Jones, L. E., Sir, 1950 Aug 30 (Box 13, Folder 650)
    - Jouhandeau, Marcel, 1955 Apr 29 (Box 13, Folder 651)
    - Jourdain, Margaret, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 652)
    - Jouve, Pierre Jean, 1953 Mar 8 (Box 13, Folder 653)
    - "K" general, 1933-87, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 654)
    - Kallin, Anna ("Niouta"), 1956-59, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 655)
      See also: BBC, Box 3, Folder 152
    - Kee, Robert, 1948 Dec 7 (Box 13, Folder 656)
    - Keen, Alan, 1957-58 (Box 13, Folder 657)
    - Kemp, Peter, 1957 Oct 9 (Box 13, Folder 658)
    - Kempner, Mary Jean, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 659)
    - Kennaway, James, 1956 Jul 2 (Box 13, Folder 660)
    - Kennington, Eric, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 661)
    - Kent, Leonard J., 1964 Sep 10 (Box 13, Folder 662)
    - The Kenyon Review, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 663)
    - Keppel, Sonia, 1933 Feb 7 (Box 13, Folder 664)
    - Ketton-Cremer, Robert Wyndham, 1931-49 (Box 13, Folder 665)
    - Key, Peter, 1961-71, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 666)
    - Keynes, Geoffrey, Sir, 1962 Feb 21 (Box 13, Folder 667)
    - Kilmartin, Joanna; Kilmartin, Terence, 19[63]-91, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 668)
    - Kinross, Patrick Balfour, Baron, 1931-76, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 669)
    - Kirkpatrick, Ivone, Sir, 1953 Nov 17 (Box 13, Folder 670)
    - Kirkup, James, 1955 Jun 8 (Box 13, Folder 671)
    - Kirstein, Lincoln, 1964-67 (Box 13, Folder 672)
    - Klemm, Helen Madeleine, 1975-77 (Box 13, Folder 673)
    - Knaplund, Paul, 1954 Jun 11 (Box 13, Folder 674)
    - Knapp-Fisher, James S., 1946-62 (Box 13, Folder 675)
    - Knickerbocker Club, 1978-94 (Box 13, Folder 676)
    - Knight, George Wilson, 1949-54, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 677)
    - Knox, James, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 678)
    - Knowles, Cyril, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 679)
    - [Kolkhorst, J. G. ?], 1931-58, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 680)
    - Kostelanetz, Richard, 1963 Oct 31 (Box 13, Folder 681)
    - Kozar, John, 1974-95, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 682)
    - Kreger, James, 1975-92 (Box 13, Folder 683)
    - "L" general, 1922-88, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 684)
    - Laffont, Robert, 1952 Feb 13 (Box 13, Folder 685)
    - Lambert, J. W., 1965 May 28 (Box 13, Folder 686)
    - Lambton, Antony, 1995 Jul 22 (Box 13, Folder 687)
    - Lancaster, Marie-Jacqueline, 1965-67 (Box 13, Folder 688)
    - Lancaster, Nancy, 1986 Dec 20, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 689)
    - Lancaster, Osbert, 19[39]-47 (Box 13, Folder 690)
    - Larrabee, Harold Atkins, 1964-69 (Box 13, Folder 691)
    - Larkin, Philip, 1958 Jun 22 (Box 13, Folder 692)
    - Lascelles, Alan, Sir, 1959 Jul 29 (Box 13, Folder 693)
    - Latham, Paul, Sir, 1936 Sep 28 (Box 13, Folder 694)
    - Laughlin, James
      See: New Directions, Box 16, Folder 868
    - Laver, James, 1932-51 (Box 13, Folder 695)
    - Lavery, Hazel, Lady, 19[32]-33 (Box 13, Folder 696)
    - Leavis, F. R., 1947 Oct 30 (Box 13, Folder 697)
    - Lee, Guy (Arthur Guy), 1958 Oct 30 (Box 13, Folder 698)
    - Lee, Joe, 1971, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 699)
    - Lee, Laurie, 1948 Jan 22 (Box 13, Folder 700)
    - Lees-Milne, James, 1956-94, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 701)
    - Lehmann, John, 1946-60, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 702)
    - Lehmann, Rosamond, 1954-56 (Box 13, Folder 703)
    - Leinster, Rafaelle Fitzgerald, Duchess of, 1979 Mar 7 (Box 13, Folder 704)
    - Lerner, Max, 1965 Aug 3 (Box 13, Folder 705)
    - Lessard, John, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 706)
    - Levi, Peter, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 707)
    - Lewis, Alun, 1941 May 19 (Box 13, Folder 708)
    - Lewis, D. B. Wyndham, 1958 Oct 8 (Box 13, Folder 709)
    - Lewis, Eiluned, 1963 Mar 1 (Box 13, Folder 710)
    - Lewis, Gweno, 1947 May 26 (Box 13, Folder 711)
    - Lewis, Rosa, 1933-39, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 712)
      One letter is addressed
      "Dear Mr. Gore"
    - Lewis, W. S., 1973 Jun 22 (Box 13, Folder 713)
    - Lewis, Wyndham, 1948-51 (Box 13, Folder 714)
    - Leyris, Pierre, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 715)
    - Liberal Central Association/Liberal Party Organization, 1939-45 (Box 13, Folder 716)
      See also: Louth Division Liberal Association, Box 14, Folder 736
    - Liebert, Herman W., 1985 Sep 25 (Box 13, Folder 717)
    - Life and Letters Today
      See: Robert Herring, Box 12, Folder 580
    - Lindsay, John V., 1966 Oct 27 (Box 13, Folder 718)
    - Lindsay, Loelia (Duchess of Westminster), [1958-81], n.d. (Box 13, Folder 719)
    - Lindsay, Martin, 1974, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 720)
    - Ling, F. H., 1947-48 (Box 13, Folder 721)
    - Linklater, Eric, 1954 Aug 4 (Box 13, Folder 722)
    - Linnit and Dunfee Limited, 1962-63 (Box 13, Folder 723)
    - Listowel, Freda Hare, Countess of, 1965, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 724)
    - Lobanov-Rostovksy, Nikita D., 1970 Oct 9 (Box 14, Folder 725)
    - Lockwood Memorial Library, State University of New York at Buffalo, 1939 May 4 (Box 14, Folder 726)
    - Loder, Mary, 1939-69, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 727-728)
    - Logue, Christopher, 1954-80, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 729)
    - London Library, 1960-63, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 730)
    - Londonderry, Edith Helen, Marchioness Dowager of (Box 14, Folder 731)
    - Longford, Christine, Countess of, 1932 Jun 21 (Box 14, Folder 732)
    - Longman, Elizabeth, 1973-86, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 733)
    - Lopokova, Lydia, 1949 Aug 4 (Box 14, Folder 734)
    - Loud, Grant, 1978, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 735)
    - Louth Division Liberal Association, 1939-40 (Box 14, Folder 736)
      See also: Liberal Central Association, Box 13, Folder 716
    - Lowe, Ian, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 737)
    - Lubbock, Percy, 1948-53 (Box 14, Folder 738)
    - Lucan, George Charles Bingham, Earl of, 1940 Jun 5 (Box 14, Folder 739)
    - Lucas, F. L., 1946-47, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 740)
    - Lunn, Arnold Henry Moore, Sir, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 741)
    - Luxmore, H. E., 1924-25, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 742)
    - Lycett, Andrew, 1994 May 21 (Box 14, Folder 743)
    - Lycett-Green, Candida, 1993-95, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 744)
    - Lympany, Moura, 1987 Feb 7 (Box 14, Folder 745)
    - Lynes, Russell, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 746)
    - Lyon, Frank H., 1944-61 (Box 14, Folder 747)
    - Lyttelton, George, 1952 Jan 27, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 748)
    - "M" general, 1933-92, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 749-750)
    - McAuley, James, 1959 Aug 25 (Box 14, Folder 751)
    - Macaulay, Rose, Dame, 1932-55, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 752)
    - McBrien, William, 1982-83 (Box 14, Folder 753)
    - McCann, C. William, 1969-87, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 754)
    - MacDiarmid, Hugh, 1956 Aug 25 (Box 14, Folder 755)
    - MacDouall, Robin, 1931-79, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 756)
    - The MacDowell Colony, Inc., 1968-79 (Box 14, Folder 757)
    - Machell, Roger, 1977-80 (Box 14, Folder 758)
    - MacInnes, Colin, 1958 Mar 14 (Box 14, Folder 759)
    - McKay, Alexandra (Box 14, Folder 760)
    - Mackenzie, Compton, Sir, 1949 Mar 9 (Box 14, Folder 761)
    - McLaren, Moray, 1959, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 762)
      letter from McLaren to Mrs.
      B. C. Horton of the BBC
    - Maclaren-Ross, J., 1950-56, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 763)
    - McLennan, Katharine, 1973-86 (Box 14, Folder 764)
    - McManus, Michael E., 1976-88 (Box 14, Folder 765)
    - The Macmillan Company, 1963-69 (Box 14, Folder 766)
    - Macnab, John D., 1977-86, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 767)
    - Madariaga, Salvador de, 1949 Jun 2 (Box 14, Folder 768)
    - Mademoiselle, 1963 Jun 6 (Box 14, Folder 769)
    - Mailáth-Pokorny, Hans, 1940-57, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 770)
    - Malcolm, Angus, 1930-59, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 771)
    - Malkovich, Mark P., 1979-85 (Box 14, Folder 772)
    - Mallon, Michael, 1994 Nov 29 (Box 14, Folder 773)
    - Mallory, Jay (Joyce Carey), 1951 Dec 2 (Box 14, Folder 774)
    - Mambrino, Jean, 1948-69, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 775)
      Letter of 5 Apr 1950 is
      accompanied by two photographs
      of Mambrino; undated letter
      is accompanied by typescript
      titled, "A L'Ombre de la
      Lumière par Jean-Xavier
      Perceval" (poems)
    - Mann, Thomas
      See: BBC, Box 3, Folder 152
    - Mannin, Ethel, 1943 (Box 14, Folder 776)
    - Manning, Olivia, 1955-61 (Box 14, Folder 777)
    - Marcel, Gabriel, 1947, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 778)
    - Margaret, Princess, Countess of Snowdon, 1957-73, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 779)
    - Margrie, William, 1952-57 (Box 15, Folder 780)
      Accompanied by flyers and
      pamphlets published by
      Margrie
    - Margulies, Erwin, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 781)
    - Mare, Jeanne de, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 782)
    - Marías, Julián, 1957-58 (Box 15, Folder 783)
    - Marina, Duchess of Kent, 1954-67 (Box 15, Folder 784)
    - Marlowe, Sylvia, 1961-80, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 785)
    - Marowitz, Charles, 1959 Nov 30, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 786)
    - Marsh, Edward Howard, Sir, 1932-47, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 787)
    - Marshall, Arthur, 1978, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 788)
    - Martin, Harry, 1961, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 789)
    - Martindale, C. C., 1948-60 (Box 15, Folder 790)
    - Masefield, John, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 791)
    - Mason, Felicity, 1981, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 792)
    - Mason, H. A., n.d. (Box 15, Folder 793)
    - Massigli, René Lucien Daniel; Massigli, Odette, 1952-55, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 794)
    - Massingham, H. J., 1932 (Box 15, Folder 795)
    - Matthiessen, Maria von
      See: Von Matthiessen, Maria, Box 24, folder 1246
    - Maugham, W. Somerset, 1935-57, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 796)
    - Maxwell, Elsa, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 797)
    - Mayer, Martin, 1959, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 798)
    - Mehta, Ved, 1962, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 799)
    - Menai, Huw, 1952 (Box 15, Folder 800)
      Letter of 19 Feb 1952 is
      accompanied by poem,
      "The Welsh Temperment"
    - Ménard, François, 1984 Jan 18 (Box 15, Folder 801)
    - Menuhin, Diana, 1980 Jan 21 (Box 15, Folder 802)
    - Mercer, Doris Gibbins, 1960-91, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 803-804)
    - Meredith, William, 1961-69, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 805)
    - Merwin, W. S., 1959 Jul 19, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 806)
    - Messel, [Oliver?], 1932 Jun 9 (Box 15, Folder 807)
      Written by a secretary
    - Methuen, Paul Ayshford Methuen, Baron, 1940 Dec 16 (Box 15, Folder 808)
    - Metropolitan Opera Association (New York, N.Y.), 1990-94 (Box 15, Folder 809)
    - Michaux, Henri, 1953 Mar 8 (Box 15, Folder 810)
    - [Millar?], Oliver [, Sir], 1957 Apr 8 (Box 15, Folder 811)
    - Miller, Robin, 1960-71, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 812)
    - Milligan, Spike, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 813)
    - Millington-Drake, Eugen, Sir, 1954 Dec 9 (Box 15, Folder 814)
    - Milner, Violet Georgina Milner, Viscountess, 1956 Feb 2 (Box 15, Folder 815)
    - Milward, Peter, 1964 Jun 3 (Box 15, Folder 816)
    - Minto, Mary Caroline Grey Elliot-Murray-Kynynmound, Countess of, 1927-40, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 817)
    - Mitchell, Julian, 1958, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 818)
    - Mitchison, Naomi, 1932 Nov 8 (Box 15, Folder 819)
    - Mitford, Jessica, 1976 Dec 20 (Box 15, Folder 820)
    - Mitford, Nancy, 1957 May 27 (Box 15, Folder 821)
    - Momcilovich, David, 1967-75, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 822)
    - Der Monat, 1957 Apr 27 (Box 15, Folder 823)
    - Montgomery, Alberta Victoria ("Betty"), 1934-40, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 824)
    - Montgomery-Massingberd, Hugh, 1957 Nov 17 (Box 15, Folder 825)
    - The Montgomeryshire Society, 1956-59 (Box 15, Folder 826)
    - The Month, 1949-61 (Box 15, Folder 827)
    - Moore, Derry (Earl of Drogheda), n.d. (Box 15, Folder 828)
    - Moore, Marianne, 1954, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 829)
    - Morgan, Charles; Morgan, Hilda, 1948-61 (Box 15, Folder 830)
    - Morgan, Evan (Viscount Tredegar), 1926-28 (Box 15, Folder 831)
      Letter of 1926 Jun 16 is
      accompanied by typescript
      and printed versions of
      APJ's poems, corrected by
      Morgan
    - Morgan, Thomas Bruce, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 832)
    - Moriarty, Michael, 1974 Jul 2 (Box 15, Folder 833)
    - Morison, Stanley, 1962 May 2 (Box 15, Folder 834)
    - Morrell, Ottoline Violet Anne Cavendish-Bentinck, Lady, [1932] (Box 15, Folder 835)
    - Morris, Carl; Morris, Hilda, 1960 Sep 22 (Box 15, Folder 836)
    - Morris, Jan, 1972 Apr 22 (Box 15, Folder 837)
    - Morrison-Bell, Clive, Sir, [1932] (Box 15, Folder 838)
    - Mortimer, Raymond, 1933-73, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 839)
    - Morton, J. B., 1931 (Box 15, Folder 840)
    - Mosley, Charlotte, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 841)
    - Mroczkowski, Przemyslaw, 1956-60 (Box 15, Folder 842)
    - Mugar Memorial Library, Boston University, 1969-70 (Box 15, Folder 843)
    - Muggeridge, Malcolm, 1949 May 30 (Box 15, Folder 844)
    - Muir, Edwin, 1950 Apr 28 (Box 15, Folder 845)
    - Munthe, Adam John, 1976 Dec 10 (Box 15, Folder 846)
    - Murat, Napoléon, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 847)
    - Murdoch, Iris, [1957], n.d. (Box 15, Folder 848)
    - Murray, John ("Jock"), 1982, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 849)
      See also: John Murray (Publishers), Box 12, folder 642
      See also: The Cornhill Magazine, Box 8, folder 302
    - Murry, John Middleton, 1955-56 (Box 15, Folder 850)
    - Museum of Modern Art (New York, N.Y.), 1961-82, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 851)
    - Myddelton, Margaret, 1965-94 (Box 15, Folder 852)
    - "N" general, 1935-91, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 853)
    - Namier, L. B., 1950-52, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 854)
    - Narayan, R. K., 1958 Jun 11 (Box 16, Folder 855)
    - National Academy of Design (U.S.), 1982-85, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 856)
    - National Broadcasting Company, Inc. (NBC), 1960 (Box 16, Folder 857)
    - National Portrait Gallery (Great Britain), 1930-61 (Box 16, Folder 858)
    - National Trust (Great Britain)/ Royal Oak Foundation, 1986-95 (Box 16, Folder 859)
      See also James Lees-Milne,
      Box 13, folder 701
    - Naval War College (U.S.), 1990-91 (Box 16, Folder 860)
    - Navrozov, Lev, 1975 May 9 (Box 16, Folder 861)
    - Nebeledne, Arcedi [?], 1990-94 (Box 16, Folder 862)
      1994 letter is a copy of a
      letter from AN to Daniel Thorne
    - Neruda, Pablo, 1961 (Box 16, Folder 863)
      Written by Jorge Sanhueza on
      on behalf of PN
    - Nevill, Anne Camilla Eveline Wallop, Lady, 1979-83 (Box 16, Folder 864)
    - Newall, Maria, 1978-80 (Box 16, Folder 865)
    - Newcastle, Henry Pelham Archibald Douglas Pelham-Clinton, Duke of, 1924-26 (Box 16, Folder 866)
    - Newby, P. H., n.d. (Box 16, Folder 867)
    - New Directions, 1956-72 (Box 16, Folder 868)
    - Newman, Ernest, 1948-49 (Box 16, Folder 869)
    - Newport Music Festival, 1974-84 (Box 16, Folder 870)
    - The Newport Review, 1977, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 871)
    - Newsday, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 872)
    - The New Statesman and Nation, 1946 Dec 9 (Box 16, Folder 873)
    - Newsweek, 1971 Jun 10 (Box 16, Folder 874)
    - The New Yorker, 1933-75, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 875)
    - New York Drama Critics' Circle, 1963 Feb 1 (Box 16, Folder 876)
    - The New York Herald Tribune, 1963-66 (Box 16, Folder 877)
    - New York Public Library, 1960-93 (Box 16, Folder 878)
    - The New York Review of Books, 1967-86 (Box 16, Folder 879)
    - The New York Times Book Review, 1951-68 (Box 16, Folder 880)
      Letter of 1968 Apr 16 encloses
      APJ's review of "The Gay Science"
      by E. S. Dallas, 1866
    - New Writing
      See: Lehmann, John, Box 13, Folder 702
    - Nichols, Roger, 1988-90 (Box 16, Folder 881)
    - Nicholson, Norman, 1948-59, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 882)
    - Nicolson, Benedict, [1952] Dec 25 (Box 16, Folder 883)
    - Nicolson, Harold George, Sir, 1931-59, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 884)
      Letter of 1950 Mar 11 encloses
      letter to HN from Derek Patmore
    - Nicolson, Nigel, 1966-68 (Box 16, Folder 885)
    - Norman, Charles; Norman, Diana, 1987 Jun 9 (Box 16, Folder 886)
    - Norrington, A. L. P., 1961 Nov (Box 16, Folder 887)
    - Norwich, John Julius, 1954-91 (Box 16, Folder 888)
    - Norwich School of Art, 1986 Oct 10 (Box 16, Folder 889)
    - "O" general, 1953-63, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 890)
    - Obermer, Nesta, [1984], n.d. (Box 16, Folder 891)
    - Obolensky, Dimitri, 1947-48 (Box 16, Folder 892)
    - O'Brien, Conor Cruise, 1954, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 893)
    - O'Brien, Edna, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 894)
    - The Observer (London, England), 1943-65 (Box 16, Folder 895)
      Letter of 1943 Feb 6 encloses
      a letter from Robert Graves to
      the editor
      See also: David Astor, Box 1, Folder 44
    - Ocampo, Victoria, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 896)
    - Old Vic Trust Limited, 1959-61 (Box 16, Folder 897)
    - Olivier, Laurence, 1977 Aug 2 (Box 16, Folder 898)
    - Onassis, Jacqueline Kennedy, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 899)
    - Osterlund, David (Box 16, Folder 900)
    - O'Sullivan, Maureen, 1973 Jun 20 (Box 16, Folder 901)
    - Oxford University Press, 1942-85 (Box 16, Folder 902)
    - "P" general, 1939-95, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 903)
    - Palmer, Herbert E., 1959 Nov 26 (Box 16, Folder 904)
    - Pankhurst, E. Sylvia, 1932 (Box 16, Folder 905)
    - Parker, Charles G., 1963-87, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 906)
    - Parker, Eric, 1950 Jun 11 (Box 16, Folder 907)
    - Parker, Robert Alexander Clarke ("Alastair"), 1950 Jul 1 (Box 16, Folder 908)
    - Parkin, Michael, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 909)
      Accompanied by copies of
      clippings about Cara Harris
      and photographs of her work,
      including a copy photograph
      of cast members from her 1937
      amateur film "Treason's Bargain,"
      which starred Osbert Lancaster,
      John Betjeman, and Cecil Beaton,
      among others
    - Parmenter, Ross, 1965 Feb 8 (Box 16, Folder 910)
    - Parsons, George, 1947, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 911)
    - Partridge, Frances, 1993 Sep 24 (Box 16, Folder 912)
    - Pavle, Prince of Yugoslavia; Olga, Princess of Yugoslavia, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 913)
    - Payne, Arthur, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 914)
    - Payson, Joan Whitney, 1967 Nov 29 (Box 16, Folder 915)
    - Pearson, John, 1975-76 (Box 16, Folder 916)
    - Pell, Claiborne, 1977-80 (Box 16, Folder 917)
    - PEN / International PEN, 1947-78 (Box 16, Folder 918)
    - Penguin Books Ltd, 1952 Jan 24 (Box 16, Folder 919)
    - Penna, José Osvaldo de Meira, 1961 Jul 6 (Box 16, Folder 920)
    - Penning-Rowsell, Edmund, 1957-72 (Box 16, Folder 921)
    - Pepin, A. B., Dr.; Pepin, R., 1935-39 (Box 16, Folder 922)
      Two letters are to Thérèse
      Pryce-Jones
    - Perry, Lionel, 1932, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 923)
    - Peter Jones (John Lewis and Company Limited), 1951-53 (Box 16, Folder 924)
    - Peterkiewicz, Jerzy, 1958 Jun 2 (Box 16, Folder 925)
    - Phelps, Gilbert, 1960-64 (Box 16, Folder 926)
    - The Phoenix Trust / The Pilgrim Trust, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 927)
    - Pilkington, Honor, 1953-[59], n.d. (Box 17, Folder 928)
    - Pilkington, Vere, 1939-80, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 929)
      Accompanied by 1954 letter
      from Lewis P. Curtis to VP
    - Pillard, Richard, 1983 Jul 11 (Box 17, Folder 930)
    - Pinero, Arthur Wing, Sir, 1932 Jun 8 (Box 17, Folder 931)
    - Pinter, Harold, 1959-60, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 932)
    - Piper, John; Piper, Myfanwy, 1940-42 (Box 17, Folder 933)
    - Pirie, Robert S., 1960-64, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 934)
    - Plimpton, George, 1967 Mar 30 (Box 17, Folder 935)
    - Plomer, William, 1948-57 (Box 17, Folder 936)
    - Pollock, Betty, 1979-82 (Box 17, Folder 937)
    - Ponsonby, Arthur Ponsonby, Baron, 1940 Aug 14 (Box 17, Folder 938)
    - Pope-Hennessy, James, 1953-58, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 939)
      Letter of 1953 Jul 5 encloses
      letter to JPH from Wilson Harris
      letter of [1954] Sep 19 encloses
      poems by Robert Pinker
    - Pope-Hennessy, John, 1985 May 10 (Box 17, Folder 940)
    - Pope-Hennessy, Una, Dame, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 941)
    - Porter, Andrew; Porter, Sheila, 1973-75 (Box 17, Folder 942)
    - Pound, Ezra, 1958-59 (Box 17, Folder 943)
    - Pounder, Robert, 1978-95 (Box 17, Folder 944)
      Accompanied by copy of Hesperia, Vol. 52, No. 3,
      1983